[Theme song]
[Ancient music]
[loudspeaker operating sound]
(Cheolwook)
Babel Chemical, an evil company, wake up!
(Tenant)
Wake up! Wake up!
(Cheolwook)
coming
[The sound of a wooden table rings]
(Yeonjin)
I can't live because I'm vomiting blood!
[Monks chant Buddha]
Reflect on Babel Chemistry!
(in advance)
This is the victims
It's a struggle of pain, everyone!
[Camera shutter sounds repeatedly]
(Chae-shin and Jeok-ha)
Bodhisattva Avalokitesvara, Bodhisattva Avalokitesvara, Bodhisattva Avalokitesvara
[Monks continue to chant]
[Rhythmic music]
What are they doing now, these bastards?
Let's go
I do it all, ah
(Chae-shin and Jeok-ha)
Bodhisattva Avalokitesvara, Bodhisattva Avalokitesvara
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Humorous sound effects]
(Judge Heo)
I lost my original intention at Persimmon Tree House and opened it.
[Laughter from the sitting judge]
The soup tastes like pie
Well, move somewhere else and go to sleep?
[The sitting judge answers]
(Yeonjin)
Oh my, my, my!
[Judge Heo groans in surprise]
Oh my, my, I’m sorry.
[Judge Heo’s disapproving groan]
[Interesting music]
- (Yeonjin) Oh, I’m sorry.
- (Judge Heo) Oh, really.
(Yeonjin)
No, this is where you buried everything.
No, I lost my lens.
Just stay still
Buried here, here, here
(Judge Heo)
Please look straight ahead.
Oh, sorry, if I do that
Stay still, pay the laundry fee.
I'll show you how to do it.
- (Judge Heo) That's it!
- (Yeonjin) Okay, is it okay?
- (Judge Heo) Oh my, that’s right.
- Sorry, sorry.
I am very sorry
Have you gone?
(Judge Heo)
When you meet the judge before trial
Don't you know it won't work, man?
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Seunghyuk)
Oh, but to my senior
I have to say hello and go in.
[Judge Heo and Seunghyuk’s laughter]
Gigi who beat me up so I could go to Ilma?
What do you say? I'll treat you well.
(Judge Heo)
Please be nice to me too, man.
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
Barbell group that always gives me headaches
They take it over
I am both physically and mentally
To my seniors and alumni association
I will repay the favor
You have to repay the favor, right?
[Interesting music]
[Judge Heo and Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Judge Heo)
without anyone knowing
(Seunghyuk)
[Laughing]
Yes, please take care of me today as well.
without anyone knowing
[Judge Heo takes a breath]
Well, I guess today will end easily?
(Judge Heo)
Well, the plaintiff's evidence is too weak.
Anyway, I'll keep my hair up.
Yes, senior
(Myunghee)
thank you
[People are murmuring]
(Seunghyuk)
What is it?
Ah, what's wrong here?
(Inspector)
Ah, suddenly the ceiling and walls
There is a water leak
We are investigating the cause
(Seunghyuk)
Oh, then we should move the court or something?
Other courts are also on trial.
(Inspector)
Please understand
(Seunghyuk)
No, I built the building like this, this
[Junwoo clears his throat]
Oh, who built this?
(Junwoo)
Babel Construction
What?
To be precise
Babel Construction’s predecessor was Haemun Construction.
Zug built it
The child carved it in stone
(Myunghee)
This is overkill
Dungdundan also breaks out at intervals of 12 solar terms.
(Seunghyuk)
Haemun Construction, this
It was just made on a whim against the country.
(Junwoo)
That's right
If you're going to eat it, you definitely need to eat it, right?
Haemun Construction is old.
Babel Construction won’t do that, right?
- Are you excited?
- (Junwoo) Huh? Yeah
(Seunghyuk)
Is it fun? Yeah, you like it?
[Junwoo’s responsive groan]
Are you here to play? Hurry up and get in there, just do it, Mr.
[Junwoo’s embarrassed groan]
(Junwoo)
Sorry, Boss
(Yeonjin)
this way
[Cheolwook answers]
[Meaningful music]
[Nervous breathing]
[Chayoung’s nervous breathing]
(Cheolwook)
Manager
I have one question to ask you.
Yes, what is it?
(Cheolwook)
When the judge comes in
They tell everyone to stand up, right?
(Joosung)
Yeah
(Cheolwook)
But what happens if you don’t wake up?
(Hongsik)
draw
[Interesting music]
I was curious about that too.
(Joosung)
Imprisonment of up to 5 years or
A fine of less than 50 million won
[People's gasps of surprise]
(Larry Kang)
Really?
[Yeonjin’s surprised moan]
That didn't happen
Hitting 5, 5,000?
It's a lie
Even if I don’t wake up, it’s no big deal.
- (Hee-su) Fish oil, Mr. I again
- (Yeonjin) Wow, really.
[Yeonjin’s laughter]
[Heesu’s sigh]
(Yeonjin)
Oh, but
Why are you asking me to get up?
uh? When did I see the judge?
(Joosung)
that
[Jusung clears his cough]
Rather than the individual judge, the
What can I say, about laws and rulings?
Does it mean respect?
- Ha, John, respect?
- (Joosung) Yes
Every time I see the news
They just make ridiculous decisions
Huh?
[Yeonjin responds]
(Cheolwook)
Man, we're all just on the side of the chaebols
I listen to you, but what
(Yeonjin)
That's right
i don't wake up
[People moan in surprise]
[Splendid music]
[Yeonjin’s laughter]
(Cheolwook)
I will show you the determination of a martial artist.
(Larry Kang)
I also have the conscience of an artist
I will show resistance
[People laughing]
We also inherit the spirit of the patriotic monks.
I won't wake up
[moktak sound effect]
[People laughing]
(in advance)
Then, as a sign of resistance, we all
Don't wake up
Huh?
[Joosung responds]
(Yeonjin)
You really don’t have to wake up, really?
Uh, sure, it's okay.
I won't catch you, I won't catch you, yeah
[Yeonjin responds]
(Hongsik)
Hey, well, then what
It's meant to unite everyone, but...
Assuming it won’t happen?
[Cheolwook responds]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, draw
(Inspector)
The judge is entering.
Everyone please stand up
[Humorous sound effects]
[The door opens]
(Hongsik)
What are you doing, Daedong Unity?
Hey, unity
(Chae Shin)
head monk
[The door slams shut]
[Nervous breathing]
[Judge Heo’s scream]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Emphasized sound effect]
[People moan in surprise]
[Interesting music]
[People are upset]
(Inspector)
Trigrams, trigrams, are you okay, Judge?
(Assistant Judge)
Oh my, why are you putting vinyl here?
[Sigh of the sitting judge]
Oh, uh, be careful
[Judge Heo’s labored breathing]
Why did you put this on vinyl?
(Inspector)
Ah, ah, yeah
There was a leak in the wall too.
In the sacred court
It's leaking water
Oh my, my waist
(Assistant Judge)
Are you okay?
[Judge Heo’s groans of difficulty]
Oh my
[Judge Heo clears his throat]
[Water drips]
According to the data submitted, researchers
(Myunghee)
Follow the safety rules stated in the manual.
[People are upset]
I ignored it and continued my research.
have been exposed to toxic substances
[Chayoung’s labored breathing]
but it
Kissing due to poor management on the part of the company
It is being claimed as an industrial accident.
Plaintiff's attorney, would you like to rebut?
[in a difficult voice]
Ah, yes
(Chayoung)
There is enough evidence to refute...
[Meaningful music]
- (Victim’s Family 1) What is it?
- (Victim's Family 2) Attorney, what's wrong?
(Victim’s family 1)
Why are you doing this?
It's enough
Ah, yes
A while ago I
Panic disorder suddenly appeared
[Myunghee laughs]
[laughter]
[People are upset]
(Victim’s family 2)
Panic disorder?
(Victim's family 3)
Did you know about panic disorder?
(Victim’s family 1)
Oh, I didn't know...
(Chayoung)
Dear Judge,
Can I take the medicine?
Oh, eat quickly, eat quickly, yeah
(Judge Heo)
Go ahead now
[Heavy breathing]
Respected Judge...
[groans with difficulty]
[Emphasized sound effect]
[People moan in surprise]
(Cheolwook)
Are you okay?
Oh my
(Yeonjin)
What should I do, huh?
(Cheolwook)
Oh my, hey, call 119 right now!
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
The mafia gambling place I know
An unexpected player
When you try to win a lot of money
There's something I'm doing for the first time.
dealer giving cards
Take it off the table.
(Chayoung)
Dealer?
What does it mean to be a dealer at trial?
- (Chayoung) Huh?
- (Vincenzo) Yes
(Cheolwook)
Are you okay?
(Inspector)
(Junwoo)
senior
(Yeonjin)
What should I do, huh?
(Junwoo)
Ah, senior, senior
Open your eyes, old man.
(Cheolwook)
Quickly call 119, 119, 119
(Yeonjin)
Oh my, what should I do?
There was a really loud noise.
Did you hear?
[Joosung’s surprised groan]
- (Cheolwook) Oh my gosh
- (Yeonjin) I heard it.
(Cheolwook)
119, 119 call, 119
(Yeonjin)
Did you hear a loud noise? Everyone heard it, right?
(Judge Heo)
Be quiet, be quiet
Damn, tsk
Lieutenant, call 119 quickly.
(Inspector)
Ah, yes
[Judge Heo clicks his tongue]
[Judge Heo clears his throat]
(Junwoo)
senior
In general, the plaintiff's representative
When there is no
It is impossible to proceed with the trial.
Today's trial is due to the seriousness of the case.
acting is difficult
[Interesting music]
(Judge Heo)
during the recess
Regarding the status of the plaintiff's representative
After collecting opinions from medical staff
Even later today
Let's get back to it, yeah
(Chayoung)
What if it doesn't work?
(Vincenzo)
What should I do? I have to wake up quickly.
[Humorous sound effects]
(Junwoo)
Wow, I’m surprised.
(Heesu)
woke up
[People moan in surprise]
(Joosung)
yes, it's okay
- (Yeonjin) Are you okay?
- (Juseong) It’s okay.
Are you awake?
(Judge Heo)
Are you okay?
yes
Once you do this, you'll be fine.
[Meaningful music]
[Junwoo clears his throat]
(Myunghee)
Why should we go again, huh?
Just by looking at it, it looks like a show.
[Embarrassed laughter]
yes
(Judge Heo)
So let's move on, yeah
Write, that, the plaintiff's attorney, plead the case.
(Chayoung)
Because the data was not submitted
I will give you a verbal explanation.
The evidence is…
[The lights suddenly turn off]
[People are upset]
(Cheolwook)
Oh my
(Yeonjin)
Oh my?
(Cheolwook)
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my
[Interesting music]
Oh, what should I do with this?
Uh huh...
(Chayoung)
What if the game goes on even if the dealer is removed?
(Vincenzo)
In that case
the entire gambling hall
Let's black it out.
(Vincenzo)
no more playing games
(Judge Heo)
Everyone be quiet, quiet
(Chayoung)
Oh my
Suddenly there is a power outage and this happens?
[Park Byun’s laughter]
Oh my
(Chayoung)
Dear Judge,
I can't argue without a stenographic record.
Wait a minute, eh, let’s take a look at the situation first…
- (Cheolwook) What are you saying?
- (Yeonjin) Yes
- (Cheolwook) Yes?
- (Miri) Judge
(in advance)
I can't hear you well because the microphone is off.
- (Yeonjin) That’s right.
- (Cheolwook) I can’t hear you, I can’t hear you.
Ah, this, well, it’s so clumsy.
I'm so embarrassed
[Clears cough]
(Judge Heo)
Is it possible to record with a laptop?
Oh, yeah, uh, wait a minute.
Please wait a moment, wait...
It's fast with a laptop
Accurate records are impossible
(Judge Heo)
It doesn't matter
Just write down the key points
[People are upset]
[Interesting music]
(Yeonjin)
Everything, I have to write it all down, everything.
(Chayoung)
Even if I do everything
What if I keep gambling?
In that case, as a last resort
They kick out all the other customers.
[Meaningful music]
Make the gambling hall a mess
- (Junwoo) I came in.
- (Myunghee) I have eyes too
yes
[Junwoo clears his throat]
[Seunghyuk sighs]
(Cheolwook)
Not yet, not yet
Shh, shh
(Yeonjin)
Calm down, okay? Shh, calm down.
(Judge Heo)
Yes, Plaintiff, go ahead.
(Chayoung)
Researchers ignored safety rules
The defendant's claim that they engaged in research
Shameless and cunning
It's so stubborn
It's a blatant lie
(Myunghee)
Your Honor
It has nothing to do with the incident
This is a meaningless personal attack.
(Judge Heo)
I admit it
Be careful!
yes
- (Yeonjin) Now, now?
- (Cheolwook) Uh, now, now
[Bees are flying around]
(Cheolwook)
What, what, huh? 'Aeng'
What is it, a disinfection truck, what is it, what is it?
What are you talking about?
(Larry Kang)
In court...
- (Yeonjin) What are you talking about?
- (Cheolwook) Oh my gosh
(Cheolwook)
Noisy, noisy, huh?
[People are murmuring]
(Judge Heo)
What are you talking about?
Who flew the drone?
Which reporter are you?
Which reporter secretly flew a drone?
[surprised]
Me, me, me, me, me!
(Hongsik)
What is that? What is that?
[Larry Kang groans in surprise]
(Cheolwook)
Huh? what?
[People moan in surprise]
[Chayoung’s surprised gasp]
(Heesu)
It's a long-lived wasp!
[People moan in surprise]
[humorous music]
(Cheolwook)
If you get stung by that, you die.
Avoid them all!
[Chayoung's voice rings]
(Chayoung)
Wake up quickly, quickly! Avoid it, quickly!
[Junwoo groans in pain]
(Junwoo)
Let's avoid it quickly, that hornet.
A very scary person even in America
If you get stung, squeal!
What to avoid!
It's crazy, really!
[Myeonghee grins]
[Bees are flying around]
[whistle]
[Myunghee laughs]
[Laughs slightly]
[Interesting music]
[People are noisy]
[laughter]
Everyone, be quiet!
(Judge Heo)
If you are not quiet
Everyone will be kicked out!
(Chayoung)
How do you make a mess in the courtroom?
Will Judge Heo also get a kick out of it?
That's a little more
I need to think about it, tsk.
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Cheolwook)
[Knocking]
Lawyer
(Chayoung)
Huh?
Uh, boss Cheolwook.
Ah, my uncle
This is wasp wine that I made myself.
Give it a try
(Chayoung)
Oh, Wasp Lord?
Oh my, oh my
[Exciting music]
[Puts the marker down]
[laughter]
- (Man 1) Now
- (Cheolwook) Yes
(Man 1)
be careful, be careful
I've knocked him out now
Be careful when you take it out later
If you do it wrong, you'll be in big trouble.
(Yeonjin)
You have to add honey first
- (Yeonjin) No, no.
- (Cheolwook) You have to add water first.
(Yeonjin)
No, honey comes first
(Cheolwook)
You have to add water first
Honey sinks to the floor
(Yeonjin)
Yes, yes, yes
[bizarre sound effect]
It was a good idea
(Cheolwook)
Yes, I have it
And add honey like this, like this
[Humorous sound effects]
[nervous music]
(Judge Heo)
Be quiet, be quiet!
[Bees are flying around]
[Moaning in pain]
(Assistant Judge)
Judge
(Judge Heo)
Oh my, it hurts, oh my
[Judge Heo sobs]
[Water drips]
wasp
[Interesting music]
(Yeonjin)
Honey, here, here? Uh, sorry.
[Cheolwook groans in pain]
(Joosung)
Still, I'm a martial artist.
I think that's about it.
(Hongsik)
It's okay, it's okay
[Cheolwook mutters]
(Yeonjin)
It must hurt so much
[Cheolwook groans in pain]
Everyone wake up
[Lonely music]
[People are murmuring]
[surprised]
Oh my
[Cheolwook and Yeonjin’s laughter]
(Hongsik)
Is your snout swollen?
(Joosung)
Wow, special makeup too.
I've never done it like that before
[Judge Heo’s groans of difficulty]
(Heesu)
It's so ugly?
What the…
[People moan in surprise]
[sigh]
[breathes and then exhales]
Everyone, please take your seats.
It's amazing, really
[sigh]
wooden avalokitesvara bodhisattva
[moktak sound effect]
[Interesting music]
[People laughing]
(Judge Heo)
[In slurred speech]
[Heavy breathing]
(Hongsik)
What are you saying?
- (Victim's Family 1) What are you saying?
- (Victim's Family 3) What, what, what?
(Judge Heo)
[Music that heightens the mood]
[People moan in surprise]
(Assistant Judge)
Judge! Are you okay?
[People are noisy]
[Myunghee’s sigh]
(Assistant Judge)
Be careful, be careful, be careful
be careful, be careful
[nervous music]
(Cheolwook)
Oh, I have to go
Hey, let's go
Wow, you worked hard, everyone.
[sigh]
[Seunghyuk laughs]
[laughter]
[sigh]
[People are noisy]
(Myunghee)
Know that you are embarrassed
[Myunghee laughs]
Let's just earn a week
How can you insult a sacred court like this?
What insult?
You are also a lawyer by name.
The method is so cruel and childish.
It's low level!
What are you saying?
Didn’t it really feel like a musical?
(Chayoung)
The start-and-run structure fits perfectly.
The climax too
[clicks tongue]
[Interesting music]
Kill it!
[laughter]
And what?
Contempt of sacred court?
The judge who came out to cover Babel Group
The idol who cheated with that judge
Are we playing around?
It's all gone, isn't it?
[Myunghee takes a breath]
(Myunghee)
Since when is our Hong Byeon
You have become an apostle of justice, right?
[surprised gasp]
(Chayoung)
no, what
Do you say such cheesy things?
I don't care about justice
Then why are you being so harsh?
Are you attacking me?
[in a playful tone]
Because I don’t want to see it.
Because I don’t want to see idols and barbells
What?
A person you don't want to see
What I want to do is hit you with a stick
Isn't it human instinct?
See you in a week
[Chayoung snorts]
[Chayoung hums]
(Myunghee)
I guess that's really true
Doesn't that seem a little crazy?
That sambara
- (Yeonjin) No, why are you burying it in your butt?
- (Cheolwook) This is how I am.
(Yeonjin)
I was so moved
Oh my, oh my, it's out, it's out, oh my!
[Hee-su responds]
[Cheers from tenants]
[The sound of a wooden table rings]
It's awesome, really!
(Heesu)
Cool, cool, cool!
[Interesting music]
Let's go
- (Yeonjin) Oh, I'm starving, I'm so hungry.
- (Chae Shin) Thank you for your hard work.
[Chayoung sighs]
[Cheolwook groans in pain]
[Yeonjin’s laughter]
(Yeonjin)
Oh, come quickly
(Chayoung)
Zoom Mugi, I’m more upset than I thought.
(Joosung)
‘Zoom weapon’?
Choi Myung-hee, Lee Moo-gi dancing Zumba
zoom weapon
(Chayoung)
It's very childish, petty, and low-grade.
A real mess
[Chayoung’s laughter]
In a mafia family
I have a family motto.
‘The strongest fist in the world’
‘It’s a fist hitting you from behind’
That's right, the fight was originally
That's cruel!
[Chayoung’s laughter]
A shameful victory is for the opponent
For causing humiliation
It works better
(Joosung)
Until next week, me too
I will prepare well
Great!
[growling sound]
Ah…
[Chayoung’s heavy breathing]
Let’s eat something and think about it a bit.
(Chayoung)
Oh, I'm so hungry
The sugar dropped a lot
(Vincenzo)
go first
I need to go somewhere
(Chayoung)
Let's eat together
No, I have to go now.
[Calm music]
(Chayoung)
Where are you going?
(Joosung)
Oh, that's right, today
It's Tuesday
Are you going there by any chance?
Where?
(Seunghyuk)
July 17, 1948
After the establishment of the Constitution of the Republic of Korea
[Myunghee’s sigh]
There are two giant hornets in the courtroom
never appeared
Huh?
There has never been one
[Junwoo groans in pain]
Ah, after 25 years of my legal career.
This is my first time seeing an asari plate like today.
First time, man, first time!
[Junwoo groans in pain]
(Junwoo)
I'm sick, boss.
- (Seunghyuk) Does it hurt?
- (Junwoo) Yes
(Seunghyuk)
Hold on, hold on, man
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on
[Seunghyuk grins]
[Moaning in pain]
(Junwoo)
yes
[Moaning in pain]
(Myunghee)
In addition, my lawyer debut
I'm completely devastated
[Myunghee’s laughter]
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, me, these dirty things, really, this
No, how do you come up with an idea?
Long-lived wasp…
[laughter]
Oh, what should I do?
If you consider it dirty
Are we the strongest kid in the country?
We ain't dirty, we ain't dirty
What is it? that
Strategic? Uh, I'm being strategic.
It's noisy, don't you think?
As they say these days, well, it's coming to an end, really.
(Junwoo)
Still, there was no trial.
There are no winners, right?
[sigh]
(Myunghee)
Why is there no winner?
We lost
(Seunghyuk)
I lost, yeah, I lost
[car horn]
These [mute sound effect] bastards
(Myunghee)
All you have to do is open your eyes!
This [mute sound effect] ** you bastards!
[Calm music]
[The door bursts open]
(Joosung)
[Sighing]
What should I do?
(Vincenzo)
Why? What's going on?
(Joosung)
Ah, yes
Lawyer Hong Yoo-chan was elected as a public official.
It's called Oh Gyeong-ja.
I'm a prisoner now
The lawyer
You really cared a lot.
Every last Tuesday of every month
Don't miss a single visit and visit us.
(Joosung)
Attorney Hong Yoo-chan is not here right now.
It must be difficult now
[The door bursts open]
(Gyeongja)
Oh my
hello
Please sit down.
[Gyeongja’s powerful moans]
How are you feeling?
[Meaningful music]
[sigh]
It's okay
There isn't much pain.
Attorney Hong Yoo-chan was not there.
I thought no one would come
Thank you for coming here
no need to be thankful
That no one will come to visit in the future
'Cause I just came to talk
Now whether it's family or friends
Ask others for help
I don't have anyone
What about your husband?
Then what about children?
[Calm music]
There is none
Ah
You have no husband or children.
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
No, well, unfair is unfair.
[laughter]
How on earth did you live your life?
How could there be no one around?
[sigh]
What is life?
It doesn't work out for everyone
(Gyeongja)
No matter how hard I try to live well
When the world doesn't allow it easily
There are more
Is this a life of making excuses?
There's probably no one around.
yes
My life was all excuses
I'm sorry you live like this, lawyer.
Not to me
Who really needs to apologize?
Spend the rest of your life thinking
(Vincenzo)
I'll just go now
(Gyeongja)
Again…
You won't have to see me, right?
I'm planning to leave here
Because this is not my country
(Gyeongja)
Lawyer
goodbye
[The door slams shut]
[sigh]
[Calm music]
[Clicks open the lighter]
[Click the lighter]
[Clicks the lighter shut]
(Vincenzo's adoptive father)
[Italian]
Are you Joo Hyung?
(Vincenzo Wool)
Joohyung, from now on we
we'll be family
[Korean]
Director
mom
(Young Vincenzo)
my mom
You said you were coming to look for me.
[Little Vincenzo sobs]
Just a little more mom
I said I was coming
Until mom comes
I have to wait
[Sobbing]
[camera shutter sound]
[Toto hums]
(Toto)
The pepperoni pizza you ordered arrived, yes.
[camera shutter sound]
If you get compliments on our blog
3 days, you will hit the jackpot within 3 days.
Thank you very much
(Blogger 1)
The party photos were posted
I heard it was very delicious
Is it similar to somewhere else?
yes?
[Interesting music]
Well, that…
(Blogger 1)
If you want a good review
You can give me all the food for free today.
(Toto)
Ah, yes
free
[Toto’s laughter]
What a boring afternoon, yeah
Well, if you savor it well,
The subtle differences unique to our Arno
You can feel it, yeah
Then
(Blogger 2)
Hey, try this too
(Blogger 1)
It's slightly irritating
(Toto)
[Knocking on the table]
Hey
Hey, they want jalapenos then
No, huh?
We ran out, huh?
And if you want a service
never give it away
Those facts, those, Mr.
(Kiseok)
yes
(Toto)
Hey, but why are you so sad?
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[shaking breathing]
[Sobbing]
yes
(Director Tae)
Are you crying?
No, crying
You had a daytime drink again and sat shivering, right?
no
[Sobbing]
where are you now?
I'm out because I have some business to do.
Hurry and rush to work now
(Director Tae)
Something urgent came up
[Call end sound]
(Kiseok)
W…
[Sad music]
[Sobbing]
sorry
[Awkward laughter]
[A rumbling sound is heard]
[Bell sound effect]
[moktak sound effect]
(Vincenzo)
head monk
(dropping)
Ah, lawyer.
(Vincenzo)
Wow
[Jeokha’s powerful moans]
Thank you for your hard work today.
no
Even the monk
Thank you for your hard work today.
But this cross...
Ah, yes
Behind them, Babel Construction Services took it away.
(dropping)
There is a church in ruins
But even after a month
This cross is on the floor
No, but what are you going to do with this?
I'm going to give it to Geumga Church in front of me.
(dropping)
To those who cherish this cross
Then
Lawyer
Could you please help me?
[Clears cough]
yes
[Bell sound effect]
[moktak sound effect]
(dropping)
Oh my, thank you, I brought it with me.
[Jeokha’s laughter]
(Vincenzo)
Monk, I have one question to ask you.
(dropping)
Please tell me
alone in a far away place
If you live only looking at the sea
in buddhism
Will all my troubles go away?
(dropping)
Hmm
The agony is
under a different sky
It's not something that exists or doesn't exist.
Under the lawyer's heart
It exists and it does not exist
[Calm music]
[laughter]
Then like monks
Do you need to become enlightened?
Agony is not the realm of enlightenment
This is the area of fight
(dropping)
Fight not to be pushed back
Enlightenment is the trophy of that fight.
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Seunghyuk)
Vincenzo and Hong Cha-young
Should I add one person?
There's no need for that.
Even if Zug flew and crawled
It's in the palm of my hand
(Seunghyuk)
Oh, what is it?
So you secretly took medicine from me again?
[laughter]
Wow, really, our Attorney Choi.
[In a charming tone]
Call the tech team
(Seunghyuk)
Technical team?
technical team
Uh, the tech team.
[Clearly and clearly]
technical team, that
[nervous music]
(employee)
It's done
(Myunghee)
That, that, that flower pot, that, that
I bought it
(Myunghee)
[In a charming tone]
Turn up the volume
This is a live broadcast
Sister, I've been doing things wrong lately.
If you get caught, you'll be in real trouble.
You scouted me to make a big deal out of it.
(Seunghyuk)
So I'm saying don't get caught.
my story is
[Seunghyuk clears his throat]
- (Seunghyuk) Now
- Write, what kind of plan is this?
The day before yesterday I heard footsteps
I could only hear music
If you keep listening to this
Something is bound to happen
[A scream comes out]
[Meaningful music]
What does this mean?
[screaming]
IC
[Larry Kang's cries come out]
[laughter]
[Larry Kang clears his throat]
[Larry Kang's roar]
Why, why are you doing this, so scary?
[laughter]
Oh, stop, I, I'm getting creepy
(Chayoung)
There's a listening device in the flower pot
How did you know?
(Vincenzo)
Ah
Stucky flower pot
Even if you don't water it for a month
It's a plant that grows well.
[Vincenzo sprays water]
[Interesting music]
Electronic listening devices that are fatal to moisture
It's so much better
[Vincenzo sprays water]
So, in the past, intelligence agencies
Planting a lot of listening devices
It was famous for its potted plants.
Well, really
Even bad things become old, ugh.
But the lawyer
You know this very well, right?
Isn’t this common sense?
[laughter]
(Chayoung)
Ah, common sense?
I really have no common sense
There really isn't any
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
(Vincenzo)
[Sprinkling water]
Not knowing is not a sin
It's a sin not to know
If there's something I don't know
Do you want to live a life of sin?
It's annoying
Oh, I asked the manager for one.
(Vincenzo)
Right next to Sangchi-dong
Well-located commercial building
Please find out one
Are you really trying to move the Plaza people?
(Vincenzo)
yes
Up to the equipment costs of all companies
I plan to pay it all
(Chayoung)
No, but
Is it really necessary to go that far?
I'll clean it up and leave as soon as possible.
[Calm music]
(Chayoung)
[Laughing]
Yeah
Then we need to find out really quickly.
Meanwhile, the people of Plaza
Lotto was right.
I need to look at some lawsuit materials.
Let's go first
(Chayoung)
Lawyer
Uh…
hmm…
[Lonely music]
[Chayoung’s surprised moan]
[Chayoung’s disgusted moans]
What is this?
Are you a wizard?
[Sparkling sound effect]
Are you from Hogwarts?
There was an after-party after our last blind date.
(Chayoung)
Green light is good
This is not it
These are clothes that make women run away.
run away, run away
Escape into my heart
Then I
(Joosung)
Lawyer, run away?
[The door clicks open]
[Calm music]
(Chayoung)
Lawyer
[The door clicks shut]
If there’s nothing going on, let’s have a strong drink, right?
Not canned beer
No, whatever you want to say
(Chayoung)
Do you drink when you have something to say?
Dimension of unity and leap forward
It's good, right?
No injections, right?
(Director Tae)
Hey!
Corn salad or corn salad?
I told you not to go into that operation!
But are you going to completely ignore what I said?
Also as a restaurant assistant?
Wow, how did you know?
What kind of stone bed company is this?
(Director Tae)
Where are you and what are you doing in 10 minutes?
It's all coming out, man!
Oh, well, that's right.
I don't know what to do with this, but it's really shit...
Ah, ah, ah
Oh my, pulling an artery, this.
sorry, sorry
(Director Tae)
Ugh, shit, shit.
[Kiseok’s sigh]
Now, look.
[Meaningful music]
About Vincenzo Cassano
Request for identity verification
I came in from two places
One is Woosang Law Firm
Another one from Babel Group
Ah, what is that silicone guy doing?
Are there requests coming from both sides?
really
Are you creating some kind of organization?
Or are you raising a slush fund?
No, as of now
There is no particular movement
Ah, but why are they making such a fuss?
I will make it into a report.
(Kiseok)
And about this request
I will send you a reply
Okay, okay.
[sigh]
(Director Tae)
Oh, and
Well, don't operate with your own money.
charge me a fee
I don't have any money, oops
- (Kiseok) I have money.
- It's a mess
(Director Tae)
Because of my mother’s surgery expenses.
You still haven't repaid the loan, you
[surprised moan]
[Calm music]
yes then
I will charge you gratefully.
Okay, go out.
Hey…
(Director Tae)
Oh my, that crybaby
Ah, ah, ah, ah
[Kiseok sobs]
[laughter]
[Atmospheric music plays]
[Chayoung’s laughter]
(Chayoung)
Ah, I burst out laughing when I saw the judge’s face.
Here and here
It feels like it's made of clay
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
They talk like parents too
[Chayoung’s laughter]
[Chayoung sighs]
True
Earlier during the day
You went to see a person named Oh Gyeong-ja, right?
How did you know?
(Chayoung)
I heard it from the office manager.
Oh Kyung-ja is that person, right?
A person falsely accused of murder
I saw it in my father's case file.
There was also an important sign.
I see.
[Chayoung sighs]
thank you
For going on behalf of my father.
(Chayoung)
I should have gone
The lawyer is better than my daughter.
No one will come now
I just came to tell you
Yes?
All of Attorney Hong Yoo-chan’s work
There's no need to take over
Now I have to do my own work as a lawyer.
I heard you are unwell.
(Vincenzo)
That's enough
Now it's time to find Geumga Plaza.
Please help me
[laughter]
Without even telling me why I was looking for it
How can I help you?
Do you really need to know why?
Of course I should know
(Chayoung)
That's how I plan, big
Tada!
[sigh]
Tsk
Then only the lawyer should know.
(Vincenzo)
You must never, ever reveal it.
What is it?
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
That…
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
Can you say ‘dugudugu’?
(Chayoung)
Drum, beat, beat…
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Vincenzo puts down his glass]
[Meaningful music]
(Vincenzo)
In the basement of Geumga Plaza
1.5 tons of gold hidden
[Interesting music]
1.5 tons?
How much is 1.5 tons?
110 million euros, in Korean Won
About 150 billion
[surprised gasp]
150 billion?
[Chayoung’s surprised gasp]
But there's a problem with this
- (Vincenzo) This gold...
- (Chayoung) Shhh
[nervous music]
Even in the basement of my house
There are 100 golden calves.
[Cow crying sound effect]
[Chayoung’s laughter]
[humorous music]
(Chayoung)
Oh, I'm going crazy
[laughter]
You feed people with something that makes people excited, right?
No, now I
Do you think I'm lying?
Attorney, is this the injection?
Talking nonsense seriously
- (Vincenzo) It’s a mess…
- (Chayoung) I sat too long.
- (Vincenzo) Mud, no, mud, over there
- (Chayoung) Let’s go, let’s go
(Vincenzo)
What does that noise mean?
yes?
(Chayoung)
Good sound, good sound, good sound
Oh, and the station also looks real.
I'll do the math
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Chayoung laughs slightly]
Let's go, Mr. Mansour Cassano.
[Chayoung’s laughter]
Mansour, Mansour
Cheonsur, Mansur, Baeksur
[sigh]
Because it's not a lie
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Yes, Mr. Joe, it is me.
Well, I brought what you mentioned to your house.
[Meaningful music]
(Vincenzo)
I guess we really have to hurry now.
I'm thinking of other ways to get the gold out.
(President Cho)
By recruiting other experts
Let's find out again
(Vincenzo)
Oh, just in case
Is there an operational blast system underground?
Let's check
Because it runs on electricity
I think you just need to detect the signal.
But whether it works
Why do you want to check?
(Vincenzo)
At least once on the system
If there was a problem and it went down
Just dig in the ground.
Without risk of collapse
(President Cho)
Okay
ask an expert
I will get a detection device and send it to you.
[Music that heightens the mood]
[People laughing]
[Each person speaks]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Kiseok’s surprised groan]
[sigh]
[Button operation sound]
[Exciting music]
[Nausea]
IC, tsk.
[The door clicks open]
[sigh]
[Humorous sound effects]
[nervous music]
[Kiseok imitates a cat’s cry]
[Music that heightens tension]
Why is it so hot here?
[urgent breathing]
[Vincenzo mutters]
[Machine operating sound]
(Kiseok)
Why are you bowing like that?
And the Italian mafia
[Meaningful music]
[Vincenzo’s groans in pain]
[Vincenzo’s groans of difficulty]
(Kiseok)
sobbing
Are you perhaps repenting?
The consiglier of the mafia
That too in front of Buddha
I bow and sob.
How did this happen?
Then, the purpose of coming to Korea is
Repentance?
[Vincenzo’s groans of difficulty]
[Vincenzo’s groans in pain]
[sigh]
It works so well, this thing.
Very perfect
It's perfect
[Moaning in pain]
[Bell sound effect]
[Each person speaks]
[Yeonjin and Heesu are humming]
Well, let me tell you something, I
Thank you to Wooyoung for all his work.
thank you so much
(Heesu)
Oh, what kind of gratitude is gratitude?
They are all our younger brothers and nephews.
He's that kind of person, isn't he?
(dropping)
Those of you who help others with compassion
He is truly a living Buddha.
(people)
Ah, yes
[Cheolwook clears his throat]
Who in the world loves wasps?
Are you taking it to court?
- (Yeonjin) Then
- Even James Bond can't do this.
[People laughing]
(Yeonjin)
Ah, but my honey’s butt is
It hasn't sunk in yet.
(Cheolwook)
Hehe
At least I come from a martial arts background, huh?
Withstand this strong poison
Look at that judge earlier, he just sucks.
[People laughing]
[Moaning in pain]
- I can't sit down yet.
- (Yeonjin) Stand, stand
Hey, hey, but we
How is Wooyoung?
Oh, first, proceed with the anti-cancer treatment.
improving condition
They say we have to wait and see.
Not the worst situation, right?
yes
(Hongsik)
Oh, well, our Wooyoung
I'm going to overcome it well
[People respond]
(Yeonjin)
Well then!
Oh, by the way, Director Larry.
today's performance
[surprised moan]
[Interesting music]
It was very intense
[Larry Kang clears his throat]
Ah, yes
Because I empathize with the victim’s pain,
I think the gesture came naturally.
(Toto)
[Imitating Lee Seon-kyun]
Ah, salami and cheese.
Vongole pasta came out.
[Toto’s laughter]
[People cheering]
Now, enjoy your meal.
(in advance)
It looks really delicious
- (Heesu) Isn’t this expensive?
- (Yeonjin) It’s very expensive.
Write, ah, I can’t go to trial.
I'm really, really sorry.
Those very famous influencer guests
I had a reservation.
You should have seen that, the trial
(Hongsik)
Wow
(in advance)
But, what do we really do?
Should I go out or not?
(Cheolwook)
Ah, it's right, it's right, it's right
I heard it from the manager
Attorney Vincenzo
Next to this, in Sangchi-dong
He asked me to look into the building.
For the purpose of our migration
[bright music]
Is that really true?
(Yeonjin)
Oh, it's not just about giving away the store.
Even the cost of our equipment
Looks like they're giving it all away
(Chae Shin)
Oh, then Nanyaksa Temple is not underground.
I'll have to ask you to do it on earth, monk.
(in advance)
About me
From the beginning, from Attorney Vincenzo’s eyes,
I felt the truth
Ha, I'm still clueless
(Heesu)
Now, what are you all going to do?
Oh, what should I do?
Either this or that
here or there
Ah, the rhyme sucks.
Of course you have to go, right?
(Cheolwook)
Yes, we should go!
[Yeonjin responds]
I want to keep fighting with Park Seok-don.
Because we have to make a living too
(Heesu)
So is everyone going?
- First of all, I call.
- (Cheolwook) Call
(Yeonjin and Hongsik)
call
(dropping)
Nose…
[moktak sound effect]
Avalokitesvara Bodhisattva
(Chae Shin)
[Imitating Lee Seon-kyun]
Hallelujah, I call too
call
a, ko, col
[Toto’s applause]
[screaming]
[eerie sound effect]
[People screaming]
(Cheolwook)
Why, why, why, why, why?
[eerie sound effect]
Uh, over there, walking back and forth in front of the station.
Aren't you homeless?
(Yeonjin)
That's right, before it rains
You're talking so loudly
(Cheolwook)
Uh, there's a name there, too.
My name is Gilbert.
(in advance)
Uh, no, why is your name Gilbert?
(Cheolwook)
I don't know, just when I'm eloping
He said he was Gilbert.
[People moan in surprise]
(Hongsik)
When did you come in? Oh my, I’m surprised.
Have a bottle of beer
(Gilbert)
Give me that one.
(Toto)
Baby, I, I, go out, go out
[People’s dissuading groans]
(Cheolwook)
It's a good day. Let me share some.
(Yeonjin)
yes
Draw, kid, how much do you want to eat?
[laughter]
(Toto)
[surprised]
No, no, no.
Ah, ah, don't just sit anywhere.
Wait a minute
[Interesting sound effects]
But we
Looks like someone I've seen a lot of somewhere?
[Interesting music]
Isn't it?
If you give me something delicious
I'll tell you some really good information
[Humorous sound effects]
[Meaningful music]
Information that will help you fix your problem
Okay, give it a try.
Let’s sell it at this age and fix it.
Everyone
You're so lucky
[Meaningful music]
(Kiseok)
The duty of an informant is
Delivering correct information
[Resolute moan]
[Keyboard operation sound]
But
[dramatic music]
[Unfortunate groan]
yes
I need to watch more
It's not time yet
[Meaningful music]
sickle old
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Mouse click sound]
[Dreamy music]
(Joosung)
Hello, good morning…
(dropping)
If you feel calm
Everyone please go in now.
(Joosung)
No, why are they acting like that this morning?
[Meaningful music]
[Mouse operation sound]
[Interesting music]
[laughter]
[sigh]
It's so perfect
[Speaks Italian]
(Seunghyuk)
A famous human rights lawyer in Milan.
Celebrity Donation King
Especially those who have been harmed by the mafia.
By taking charge of the defense
They say they get death threats all the time.
[Myunghee takes a breath]
Is this really true?
Italian organized crime officer
I sent it to you directly.
Ha, this is funny, huh?
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[surprised moan]
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
(Seunghyuk)
yes
[in a low voice]
Babel Chapter President
Yes, child, no, yes
Yes? Today?
[nervous music]
(Chayoung)
On the second anniversary
You must come forward as witnesses.
And to my questions and the defendant's expected questions:
You need to prepare
Can we do well?
(Vincenzo)
don't worry too much
We can just exchange questions as promised.
The defendant's expected questions are:
We will give away samples
Manager
(Chayoung)
From now on, you need to brace yourself.
The lawyer over there is very selfish.
[sigh]
(Seunghyuk)
[Flicking through documents]
No, I'm so busy.
Why are you suddenly giving me a status briefing again?
No, this is something that will call me out too, is this?
Babel Pharmaceutical, construction, chemistry, this
how it works
Isn’t it obvious to them too?
I don't think I just called it.
When you go, you'll know why.
(Seunghyuk)
Jang Jun-woo, man, you’re good at briefing, huh?
Don't hesitate again
(Junwoo)
Yes?
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes
(Seunghyuk)
Like this, like this, like this, huh?
This is already stuttering, this
'Yes, yes, yes, yes'
Oh my, Mr.
Ah, you came to have fun, huh?
- (Junwoo) Ah, no, yes, ah, no
- What should I do with him?
(Seunghyuk)
Idiot partner, take this
Idiot partner, yes
Hehe, is it funny? Isn't it funny? Hehe
[Junwoo is humming]
(Myunghee)
Let's be quiet
[nervous music]
(Seunghyuk)
He came to play, he, he came from work to play.
(Myunghee)
Write, child
[humming]
[Chayoung takes a breath]
(Chayoung)
How do you predict the win rate on the 2nd day?
(Vincenzo)
our witnesses
Assuming you do it right
40%?
Oh, still better than the first time
The odds have gone up significantly?
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
We requested witnesses for our side, right?
Yes, we have applied to the court and it will be reviewed.
(Vincenzo)
[Clicking lighter]
When Director Gil of Haemun Hospital appears as a witness,
we'll probably be pushed out
[Sighing]
We can trust it too
I need medical advice
We'll all go out, right?
Exactly until yesterday evening
I got advice from 56 doctors.
(Vincenzo)
Originally, medical advice for industrial accident cases at large corporations.
It is not easy to obtain in any country.
There is no possibility of our witnesses being bribed, right?
There are people who have a strong antipathy toward Babel.
It's unlikely, but
But what?
witnesses in a different way
I might touch it
(Chayoung)
Then we too
We need to touch the witnesses over there.
(Vincenzo)
In times like this
We need to find and attack the Witnesses' enemies.
Because the enemy of my enemy is my friend
[Vincenzo clicks his lighter]
[Interesting music]
[Juseong’s elasticity]
I'm excited again
Touching the other side's witnesses
I could never have imagined it in my dreams
So let's start by shaking off the enemies of our enemies.
(Seunghyuk)
[in a low voice]
I have to do it
to start
(Junwoo)
Ah, ah
[Junwoo clears his throat]
Okay, from now on
Let's start the briefing
[laughter]
[Button operation sound]
[Splendid music]
[Junwoo’s laughter]
From now on, we reveal the secrets of Babel Group.
(Junwoo)
Wow!
'The Secret of Babel'
[Seunghyuk’s awkward laughter]
We had some fun preparing it
[Junwoo sighs]
(Junwoo)
Founder of Haemun Group, the predecessor of Babel Group
To Chairman Kook-hwan Jang,
had two sons
[Button operation sound]
[nervous music]
The first son is from his original wife, Mrs. Hwang Sook-jin.
The second son is
pale young secretary
I was born from a woman named Seo Min-hee.
[laughter]
Just do your work, why are you having an affair?
[Seunghyuk’s embarrassed groan]
(Seunghyuk)
Hey, ah, hey, Jang Jun-woo
[Meaningful music]
What are you doing, man!
Jang Jun-woo, you bastard, come in
Stay still
No, are you still?
- (Chinese) Sit down, sit down
- sit down
- (Chinese) Sit down quickly, quickly.
- (Seunghyuk) Sit down quickly.
[sniffles]
Okay, then first
Who is the second son here?
(Junwoo)
right away, right away, right away
Chairman Jang Han-seo!
[Button operation sound]
[Junwoo and Hanseo cheer]
Is it you, tell me
[Junwoo’s laughter]
[laughter]
[Seunghyuk’s awkward laughter]
[Junwoo’s laughter]
Okay then
Who is the first son?
[shaking breathing]
[Magnificent music]
Ha, since I was young
Smart, active
Always never miss first place
Although I am not a senior at Stanford Law School,
Graduated with excellent grades
Possessing charisma
Perfect and perfect visual of God!
Who is he?
who?
[laughter]
[Button operation sound]
Its me
Junwoo Jang
[intense music]
[Embarrassed groan]
Real owner of Babel Group
Jang Jun-woo!
[cheering]
(Junwoo)
Hanseo, are you ready?
♪ Tonight’s star is ♪
(Junwoo and Hanseo)
♪ It's me, it's me, it's me, it's me ♪
(Junwoo)
♪ Babel Group is actually
It's mine, it's mine ♪
- ♪ It’s my brother’s ♪
- (Junwoo) Oh, it’s mine.
Surprise!
(Junwoo)
♪ Actually, Babel Group is mine ♪
[Seunghyuk cheers]
[Hanseo and Seunghyuk cheer]
[Noisy]
(Junwoo)
What a man!
- (Junwoo) I didn’t know.
- (Hanseo) I didn’t know.
(Junwoo)
Actually it's mine, it's mine
Mine, mine!
mine, mine
Mine!
[Meaningful music]
(Seunghyuk)
sorry
Please forgive my rudeness so far.
[Junwoo’s laughter]
(Junwoo)
Hey, it's okay, I had fun, yeah
Did you have fun too?
[Junwoo’s laughter]
Ah, yes, of course, brother.
What, I ride a roller coaster every day
That's how I felt
[Hanseo’s laughter]
(Junwoo)
sit down, sit down
(Seunghyuk)
yes
Me and Chairman Jang Han-seo
(Junwoo)
Hmm, doesn't it look like a robot vacuum cleaner?
I'm working hard, but I'm 20% lacking?
(Seunghyuk)
Oh no, no, no, no, no
Ah, really, really, just like that
You both are amazing
No, no, he's brilliant.
So, infinitely
very capable
Those are the brothers.
[Seunghyuk’s awkward laughter]
[laughter]
(Junwoo)
Hey, what's wrong?
Do what you do
stupid boss
(Seunghyuk)
How...
[Laughing]
Oh, you idiot!
Yeah, I'm being a bit clumsy.
Yes, it's a bit much to do
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
I'm embarrassed
(Chinese book)
From now on, my brother
I will treat you well as the official chairman.
Maintain confidentiality well.
(Seunghyuk)
yes
(Junwoo)
What's wrong?
Who cares if it's the president, huh?
(Myunghee)
no
Now that you know, Chairman
You need to treat him like a real chairman.
[Awkward laughter]
By the way, Attorney Choi.
[Meaningful music]
I heard you asked me to buy the Southeastern District Prosecutor’s Office?
yes
(Junwoo)
Whether it is the chief prosecutor or the judge.
A list of necessary purchases
Please select a quote
After review
I will press the purchase button
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
I will post a quote
(Junwoo)
That's it, huh?
Yesterday's trial was a bit of a disappointment.
I can't even see it properly
(Chinese book)
No, these days, whatever.
Doesn't do anything right, the idol
Brother now
How patient are you, tsk
(Myunghee)
sorry
What will happen in vain in the future
There won't be
A knifeman at the Southeastern District Prosecutor’s Office?
(Junwoo)
Well, I heard you said that.
But in my eyes
Vincenzo looks more like a sword master.
Do you know Attorney Vincenzo well?
How do you not know
He's the guy who blew up my Babel Pharmaceutical warehouse.
(Chinese book)
Put 50 syringes in my pillow
That’s him too, right?
(Junwoo)
If it's hard to win
Attorney Hong Yoo-chan
Like Babel Pharmaceutical researchers
Handle it ignorantly
It's easy and good
Please watch from now on.
[laughter]
(Junwoo)
Yeah
yes
[Junwoo sighs]
Take good care of my younger brother too.
Don't ignore it as fake, eh?
(Seunghyuk)
yes, i understand
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Junwoo)
Right?
[Laughing]
yes
(Seunghyuk)
Please go in
[The door clicks open]
[The door slams shut]
[Puts down the glass]
[Myeonghee’s powerful moans]
[Myunghee’s sigh]
[Myunghee’s angry groan]
[Myunghee’s heavy breathing]
[Rough breathing]
[Myunghee’s angry groan]
[Angrily moaning]
(Junwoo)
A knifeman at the Southeastern District Prosecutor’s Office?
[nervous music]
But in my eyes
Vincenzo looks more like a sword master.
[Angrily breathing]
[Rough breathing]
[Call connection tone]
(Myunghee)
From now on
The board is completely remade in 5 hours.
(Man 2)
Hey there
- Yes?
- (Man 2) Yes, hello.
(Man 2)
Hey, is there a meeting for victims of the Babel Chemical Industrial Accident?
Are you the accounting secretary?
Yes, by the way
[Music that heightens the mood]
[ECG meter beeping sound]
(Myunghee)
And finally
It will be broadcast on the morning news at exactly 6 o'clock.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[surprised moan]
[Chayoung sighs]
[Meaningful music]
(Chayoung)
Manager, why so early…
(Joosung)
Lawyer, check the news quickly now.
(Anchor on TV)
According to Daechang Ilbo exclusive coverage,
Representatives of families of Babel chemical industrial accident victims
The donations were stolen
Found to be useful for 2 years
What is this again, Mr. Lee?
[intense music]
(Victim's family 3)
Hey, if you look closely, we are really…
No, detective.
(Victim’s family 2)
Uh, lawyer.
What should I do? Please help us.
What's going on?
[Victim Family 2 sobs]
(Detective)
Are you a lawyer?
(Chayoung)
yes
There is clear evidence
Did you arrest him?
Evidence?
(Detective)
Oh, there are too many to organize.
[nervous music]
In their cars, in their homes
On the ceiling of the meeting room, etc.
A bundle of cash came out.
It's money stolen from donations.
Is there any evidence of embezzlement?
That's him over there
(Detective)
The treasurer of this group confessed
[Victim’s Family 1’s surprised moans]
By forcing and threatening to manipulate accounting
I had no choice but to take the money out.
(Victim's family 3)
Oh, no, lawyer.
It's really unfair to us
It has nothing to do with money, okay?
(Victim's family 4)
No, lawyer, yes?
(Victim’s family 1)
It's money I don't know, I don't know.
(Victim’s family 2)
Lawyer, you know.
We feel really unfair.
Lawyer, please help me, okay?
Uh, lawyer, we're really unfair.
We're not really
[sigh]
[Chayoung sighs]
Choi Myung-hee should be sent to the film industry.
(Chayoung)
What kind of lawyer writes a screenplay?
I'm better at directing
no, and
Why do lies work so well?
Tsk
The power of lies
The power of a liar
Because it’s directly proportional
[sigh]
(Chayoung)
They all have to testify.
This makes it difficult to adopt a witness.
(Vincenzo)
Even if you are chosen as a witness and come to court
Choi Myung-hee will become prey.
It becomes more disadvantageous for us.
In the end, the only witnesses left to us are
It's just Wooyoung Lee in the hospital.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Chayoung)
Yes, manager.
Yes, I just got a call from the court.
The witnesses were cancelled?
(Joosung)
That's it too
Lee Woo-young's adoption was also canceled.
[nervous music]
Are you Wooyoung Lee?
(Chayoung)
Why?
(Joosung)
I did a drug test on him.
A small amount of heroin was detected.
They say they have to investigate.
Heropon?
[laughter]
(Chayoung)
I got it first, manager.
[Chayoung’s exclamation]
Awesome
The confirmation kill was amazing.
Choi Myung-hee really looks like a mafia
Write
Even the mafia doesn't do this these days.
[sigh]
(Junwoo)
senior
(Chayoung)
Why? Did you come to check if it was bombed?
Hey, why are you talking like that again?
I came to check because I had something to brief.
(Chayoung)
Then go and check it out.
(Junwoo)
senior
Come back to Idol
[laughter]
Are you the representative of Idol?
Boss told me to tell you
(Junwoo)
With lawyer Choi Myung-hee
I'll treat you the same
Make a comeback
Oh my, I got hit by a wasp once.
I guess it's disappointing
It's okay, so be it.
(Junwoo)
Why with such good skills
Do you keep doing hard work?
What about a barbell?
Why So Serious?
(Chayoung)
Why are you so serious all of a sudden, you?
(Junwoo)
Senpai, you keep suffering needlessly.
Now I'm angry
[laughter]
and
Since the two of you were together
The way we work has also become strange.
(Chayoung)
Junwoo Jang
I said this clearly before, right?
Don't cross the line
I'm saying this because I'm worried.
Can you please listen to me?
Yeah, no.
You mind your own territory
(Chayoung)
Let's go in, to discuss measures.
(Junwoo)
Lawyer
Hmm
[Meaningful music]
In a Korean proverb
There is one thing that impresses me the most.
‘He digs his own grave’
I don't want my senior to go to the grave.
Helping dig the grave
I don't like lawyers either.
[Junwoo sighs]
I'm a lawyer
I think he's a very smart person.
The smarter the person is
I knew the right time to stop.
[laughter]
Let me tell you two things.
(Vincenzo)
We're digging a grave, right?
But
The epitaph is not us
And smart people
It's not time to stop
Timing when the opponent becomes weak
I know it well
[laughter]
[Vincenzo laughs]
I am learning well from my idol.
You'll be a great lawyer
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
See you next time
(Chayoung)
Huh, really
[Chayoung sighs]
After my father did that, what?
Comeback?
Oh, they're just such shameless bastards
[Chayoung sighs]
(Vincenzo)
If you're cornered
I'm bound to be insulted
Hey there
(Chayoung)
In times like this, encourage me
Can't you say something hopeful?
Hopeful words?
[Snaps fingers]
Oh, that
‘In a battlefield where there is no chance of winning, giving up is also an opportunity.’
What hope is that...
[Calm music]
[Chayoung’s angry groan]
(Chayoung)
I'm just so annoyed, just, so just
Oh, I don't know
Do it alone, no witnesses, whatever.
Yeah, life is all alone
I'll take a walk to cool off.
The lawyer will take care of the car.
[Chayoung’s crazy laughter]
Now all you have to do is talk alone in court.
[Chayoung’s laughter]
Oh, what should I wear that day?
[Meaningful music]
[The door slams shut]
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Seunghyuk)
Ah
(Junwoo)
Thanks, boss
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, this door, just
[door rattling]
Going back and forth in both directions
(Junwoo)
Hi, senior
There are no witnesses there today, are they?
(Myunghee)
Of course
All requests for witnesses were rejected.
Okay
[laughter]
[buzzing sound effect]
Mom, hey, what is this mesh, this?
What, see-through?
(Myunghee)
Oh, my judge.
I'm afraid the wasps will come out again
They called an expert.
trauma
[laughter]
Oh, uh, Chairman.
- (Seunghyuk) Are you here?
- (Chinese book) Go, sit, go, sit
(Seunghyuk)
This way, yeah
[laughter]
Ah, yes
Please take care of me today as well
Ah
[Clears cough]
Today, from the beginning, Director Gil of Haemun Hospital
Let's just push it all away
Yo
good luck
Thank you
(Inspector)
Everyone wake up
[The door slams shut]
[pulls out a chair]
Everyone please sit down
[sigh]
[Meaningful music]
(Director Gil)
Therefore
The plaintiff's argument makes no sense.
not everyone was healthy
They were people who enjoyed smoking and drinking.
Other victims of Babel Chemical also
It was similar to this
That's it.
[Nervous moaning]
(Judge Heo)
There isn't a single witness accepted?
Do you have any more witnesses to apply?
(Chayoung)
Dear Judge,
Apply for financial witness
Financial witness?
[Interesting music]
What is this again? Tsk
(Judge Heo)
That…
Does anyone have information about the case?
Yes, I am a person with clear information.
(Judge Heo)
That…
Just come in, yeah
Come in.
financial witness
[Interesting music]
This is financial witness Vincenzo Cassano.
[intense music]
[Rhythmic music]
(Vincenzo)
A card that has no choice but to be taken out
There is one
[People are noisy]
(Vincenzo)
most common way
(Junwoo)
Creativity is something you're born with
Like Vincenzo Cassano!
(Junwoo)
Take away everything you have
(Chayoung)
Then let's do something
(Junwoo)
Shut up and destroy it quickly
(President Cho)
Merchants may get hurt
(Vincenzo)
invisible equator
There are times when I accidentally leave a mark.
I need to find it
(Vincenzo)
Presents conclusive evidence
(Junwoo)
Because you will fall straight to hell
[ECG monitor beeps]
(Vincenzo)
If you do something wrong, you have to pay the price.
[Junwoo’s angry groan]
(Vincenzo)
I will definitely make you pay
Subtitle: Kwon Jeong-won